Finding Aid for the Stanley Kramer Papers LSC.0161
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Films, (Document Boxes)
  - Secret of Santa Vittoria
    - Scripts
      - 11. Combined continuity. (5)., September 23, 1969 (Box 223)
      - 12. Combined continuity, (6)., September 23, 1969 (Box 224)
      - 13. Script (2), April 18, 1968. (Box 224)
      - 14. Script, 8 parts (in Italian). (Box 225)
      - 15. First draft. Ben Maddow., From blue cover. (Box 225)
      - 16. First draft. Bill Rose., Old script typed. (Box 225)
      - 17. Replacement from yellow draft. Ben Maddow. (Box 225)
      - Script. Screenplay by William (?) and Ron Maddow., April 18, 1968.; Bound copy with notations. (Box 298)
    - Stills
      - 1. Production stills, Approximately 1400. (Box 226, Box 227, Box 228)
    - Tapes
      - 1. Quinn Tape #1, #2 & #3. (Box 229)
      - 2. Radio Commercial (Cinzano). (Box 229)
      - 3. Interviews of major actors in Secret. (4) (Box 229)
    - Miscellany
      - 1. Scores (2). (Box 358)
      - 2. Stack of postcards (Location). (36) (Box 230)
      - 3. Audience Reaction cards, Approximately 500. (Box 230)
      - 4. Sample Invites and Tickets--Previews. (Box 230)
      - 5. Stereo album--original score (2). (Box 334)
      - 6. Clippings, newspaper (1).
      - 6a. Clippings, newspaper (1). (Box 231)
      - 7. Clippings, Foreign, Trade, Magazine. (Box 232)
      - 8. Press Kit. (Box 232)
      - 9. Proofs. World premiere--Village Theatre, Westwood., October 17, 1969. (Box 232)
      - 10. Il Segreto di Santa Vittoria. di Robert Crichton. (Box 232)
        Translation by Ugo Carrega. With correspondence.
    - Folders
      - 1. Awards, Academy Nominations etc. (Box 206)
      - 2. Audley, Michael (Dialogue Director). (Box 206)
      - 3. Assets Recoverable. (Box 206)
      - 4. Anticoli Corrado, Italy (Location). (Box 206)
      - 5. Actors Hirec in Europe (ContractS). (Box 206)
      - 6. Budget--Estimated Detail. (Box 206)
      - 7. Budget--Cost Reports & Trial Balances. (Box 206)
      - 8. Box Office Receipts. (Box 207)
      - 9. Beck, Myer Pages--Correspondence, Sales, etc. (Box 207)
      - 10. Beck, Myer Pages (Sales Representative)--Agreement. (Box 207)
      - 11. Programs. (Box 207)
      - 12. Production Notes. (Box 207)
      - 13. Chuck Painter (Personal Data & Instructions).
      - 14. Los Angeles Premiere. (Box 207)
      - 15. Jerry Pam & Associates. (Box 207)
      - 16. Premieres / Previews--Correspondence. (Box 207)
      - 17. Preview Lists. (Box 208)
      - 18. Press Junkets. (Box 208)
      - 19. Promotion--Miscellaneous Projects. (Box 208)
      - 20. Pages A. Tours. (Box 208)
      - 21. Television & Radio Promotion (2). (Box 208)
      - 22. Book Promotion & Sales. (Box 208)
      - 23. Promotion (Cinzano) thru, December 31, 1968. (Box 209)
      - 24. Promotion (Cinzano) from, January 1, 1969. (Box 209)
      - 25. Photographers & Photo Coverage. (Box 209)
      - 26. Los Angeles Premiere Meetings. (Box 209)
      - 27. Press Lists. (Box 209)
      - 28. Press Conferences. (Box 209)
      - 29. Photo Orders. (Box 209)
      - 30. Photos--Key Set Correspondence. (Box 209)
      - 31. Shooting Schedule. (Box 209)
      - 32. United Artists Corporation--Financing & Distribution Agreement. (Box 209)
      - 33. Editorial. (Box 209)
      - 34. Dubbing - Foreign. (Box 210)
      - 35. Dragon, Carmen. (Box 210)
      - 36. Distribution Statements, monthly from UA. (Box 210)
      - 37. Directors Guild of America. (Box 210)
      - 38. de Rossi, Alberto (make-up man). (Box 210)
      - 39. De Laurentiis, Dino. (Box 210)
      - 40. Day out of Days. (Box 210)
      - 41. DeFilippo, Eduardo. (Box 210)
      - 42. Daily Production Reports (2). (Box 210)
      - 43. Crichton, Robert (author)--Correspondence. (Box 210)
      - 44. Crichton, Robert (author)--agreement. (Box 210)
      - 45. Crew--Miscellaneous Correspondence. (Box 210)
      - 46. Credits--Main Title & Advertising. (Box 210)
      - 47. Comments, Congrats, Quotes, etc. (Box 210)
      - 48. Clatworthy, Robert (Production Designer). (Box 210)
      - 49. Claims - Gabriella Nardi & M. Coccioletti. (Box 210)
      - 50. Credits--Conflict (Joe King). (Box 210)
      - 51. Cinzano Vermouth. (Box 211)
      - 52. Cinecitta Studios. (Box 211)
      - 53. Chemical Bank New York Trust Company (Loan). (Box 211)
      - 54. Cast & Crew Lists. (Box 211)
      - 55. Casting Director - Rome (Anna Grisi). (Box 211)
      - 56. Call Sheets (2). (Box 211)
      - 57. Butler - Glouner Incorporated (Main Title Credits) Correspondence. (Box 211)
      - 58. Lisi, Virna (Contract). (Box 211)
      - 59. Lee, Danny (Special Effects). (Box 211)
      - 60. La Bella, Joe (Prop. Man). (Box 211)
      - 61. Kruger, Hardy (Contract). (Box 211)
      - 62. Kramer, Stanley--Expense Accounts. (Box 211)
      - 63. Kramer, Stanley--Correspondence. (Box 211)
      - 64. Kramer, Stanley--Villas. (Box 211)
      - 65. Kramer, Karen--Correspondence. (Box 211)
      - 66. Kramer, Earl. (Box 211)
      - 67. King, Joe (Costumer). (Box 212)
      - 68. Insurance & Claims. (Box 212)
      - 69. Hacker & Company, Samuel (New York). (Box 212)
      - 70. Gosnell, Ray (1st Assistant Director). (Box 212)
      - 71. Gold, Earnest (Composer) Contract. (Box 212)
      - 72. Gifts, Thank You letters from Rome (Cast & Crew). (Box 212)
      - 73. Giannini, Giancarlo--Contract. (Box 212)
      - 74. Franchi, Sergio--Contract. (Box 212)
      - 75. Film Effects of Hollywood. (Box 212)
      - 76. Festival--San Francisco, October 22, 1969. (Box 212)
      - 77. Reviews. (Box 212)
      - 78. Releases--#1. (Box 212)
      - 79. Releases--#2. (Box 212)
      - 79a. Releases--#3. (Box 212)
      - 80. Releases--Features, Column Items. (Box 213)
      - 81. Releases--UA. (Box 213)
      - 82. Releases--dates. (Box 213)
      - 83. Synopsis. (Box 213)
      - 84. Trailers. (Box 213)
      - 85. United Artists Publicity Manual. (Box 213)
      - 86. San Francisco Film Festival. (Box 213)
      - 87. Roy Newquist Project. (Box 213)
      - 88. Music. (Box 213)
      - 89. Magazine Coverage. (Box 213)
      - 90. Mailings, Correspondence--Lists. (Box 213)
      - 91. Mailings, Perm, Record. (Box 214)
      - 92. Machiavelli quotes. (Box 214)
      - 93. Locations. (Box 214)
      - 94. Grosses. (Box 214)
      - 95. Film Clips. (Box 214)
      - 96. Expenses--Italian Publicity Office. (Box 214)
      - 97. Robert Crichton--Italian Assignment. (Box 214)
      - 98. Correspondence--Miscellaneous (2). (Box 214)
      - 99. Cast & Crew. (Box 214)
      - 100. Budgets. (Box 214)
      - 101. Billing. (Box 214)
      - 102. Billboards. (Box 215)
      - 103. Advertisements. (Box 215)
      - 104. Academy Awards, 1969-1970. (Box 215)
      - 105. Academy Awards and Golden Globe, (accordion folder)., 1969-1970 (Box 215)
      - 106. Screenings. (Box 216)
      - 107. Seattle Opera Association. (Box 216)
      - 108. Zagon, Schiff, Hirsch & Levine (correspondence). (Box 216)
      - 109. Wyman, Don (Location Auditor). (Box 216)
      - 110. Werner, Oskar--Contract. (Box 216)
      - 111. Publicity--Campaign Outline. (Box 216)
      - 112. Publicity--Appearances. Television, radio, personal and telephone interviews. (Box 216)
      - 113. Programs & Invitations. (Box 216)
      - 114. Production Notes--Synopsis etc. (Box 216)
      - 115. Preview--Sneak (San Diego). (Box 216)
      - 116. Premiere, Los Angeles. (Box 216)
      - 117. Premiere--Correspondence. (Box 216)
      - 118. Panavision--Rome--Agreement). (Box 216)
      - 119. Newquist, Roy (Freelance Writer). (Box 216)
      - 120. Negative--Technicolor--Rome. (Box 216)
      - 121. Negative--Technicolor--Hollywood. (Box 216)
      - 122. Publicity--Advertisements. (Box 216)
      - 123. Negative--Technicolor--London. (Box 216)
      - 124. Negative--Correspondence. (Box 216)
      - 125. Music Spotting Notes. (Box 216)
      - 126. Music--Miscellaneous Correspondence. (Box 216)
      - 127. Music--Song, O Sole Mio. (Box 216)
      - 128. Music--Conflict. (Box 216)
      - 129. Music--Song, Ziggo Ziggo. (Box 216)
      - 130. Music--Song from Santa Vittoria. (Box 216)
      - 131. Music--Song, Tzigo Tzigo. (Box 216)
      - 132. Music--Song, Stay. (Box 217)
      - 133. Music--Song, Giovanezza. (Box 217)
      - 134. Music--Song, Bella Bimba. (Box 217)
      - 135. Music--Cue Sheet. (Box 217)
      - 136. Music--Bob Tracy Music Cutter File. (Box 217)
      - 137. MPAA (Motion Picture Association of America). (Box 217)
      - 138. Morris Org. SPA. (Box 217)
      - 139. Magnani, Anna (Contract). (Box 217)
      - 140. Locations. (Box 217)
      - 141. Maddow, Ben (writer)--Contract. (Box 217)
      - 142. Volkman, Ivan--Production Manager. (Box 217)
      - 143. United Artists Corporation--Contractual Delivery Requirements. (Box 217)
      - 144. United Artists Corporation--Miscellaneous Correspondence. (Box 217)
      - 145. Television Featurettes. (Box 217)
      - 146. Theatre Openings. (Box 217)
      - 147. Technicians--Italy. (Box 217)
      - 148. Synopsis. (Box 217)
      - 149. Speeches (S. Kramer). (Box 217)
      - 150. Simon & Schuster--Publisher (correspondence). (Box 217)
      - 151. Simon & Schuster - Publisher (Advertising). (Box 218)
      - 152. Schlom, Marshall (Script Supervisor). (Box 218)
      - 153. Salaries--Italian crew. (Box 218)
      - 154. Rotunno, Pepe (cameraman) Contract. (Box 218)
      - 155. Rose, William (writer) Contract. (Box 218)
      - 156. Reviews--Book. (Box 218)
      - 157. Research. (Box 218)
      - 158. Rascel, Renato (Contract). (Box 218)
      - 159. Quinn, Anthony (Contract). (Box 218)
      - 159a. Publicity. (Box 218)
      - 160. Publicity--United Artists--Correspondence. (Box 218)
      - 161. Publicity--Miscellaneous from G. Glass (Rome). (Box 218)
      - 162. Publicity--Tie-ups--Commercials. (Box 218)
      - 163. Publicity--Sumner, Gabe--Correspondence. (Box 218)
      - 164. Publicity--Spot Announcements. (Box 218)
      - 165. Publicity--Press Releases. (Box 218)
      - 166. Publicity--Press Correspondence. (Box 218)
      - 167. Publicity--Pre-production and production budgets. (Box 218)
      - 168. Publicity--News Clippings. (Box 218)
      - 169. Publicity--Italian. (Box 218)
      - 170. Publicity--Goldberg, Fred--Correspondence. (Box 219)
      - 171. Publicity--George Glass. (Box 219)
      - 172. Publicity--Foreign--General. (Box 219)
      - 173. Signed releases for Television Special. (Box 219)
      - 174. Stills, Captions. (Box 219)
      - 175. Rose, William (writer)--Correspondence. (Box 219)
      - 176. Publicity--United Artists release. (Box 219)
      - 177. Artists and artwork. Anticoli. (Box 219)
    - Medallion given by the Mayor of Anticoli Corrado, Italy, for The Secret of Santa Vittoria. (Box 123)
      See also: Boxes 328-332, 339, 341, 356, 371.
  - Sheiks of Araby
    - Movement Lists (Empty). (Box 233)
    - MPAA (Motion Picture Association of America). (Box 233)
    - Kiliper, R. Smith. (Box 233)
    - Cast & Crew Lists. (Box 233)
    - 15. Howard Borris. (Box 233)
    - Budget--Estimated Detail. (Box 233)
    - Actors & Agents. (Box 233)
    - Correspondence
      - General Correspondence. (Box 233)
      - Schiff, Hirsch & Levine--Correspondence. (Box 233)
      - William Morris--Correspondence. (Box 233)
      - Music--Miscellaneous Correspondence (Empty). (Box 233)
      - Claim (Judy Belle and the Poorest Millionaire). (Box 233)
      - #10497--Correspondence. (Box 233)
    - Contracts
      - Paramount Pictures--Agreement. (Box 233)
      - Universal. (Box 233)
      - Sherman, Stanford--Contract. (Box 233)
    - Publicity
      - Publicity Releases--Beck, Meyer Pages--Correspondence. (Box 233)
      - Publicity Releases. (Box 233)
    - Scripts
      - Draft B, It's a Bad, Bad, Bad, Bad World. (2). (Box 233)
      - Work order for first draft., Approximately 300 leaves. (Box 239)
      - Script - Revised pages, July 14, 1975. (Box 233)
      - First draft:, July 28, 1975. (Box 233)
      - First draft - obsolete, July 28, 1975. (Box 234)
      - First revised draft - Revised pages, (with S. Kramer notes)., December 15, 1975 (Box 234)
      - Revisions, (with S. Kramer notes)., December 17, 1975 (Box 234)
      - First draft: (with S. Kramer notes)., May 20, 1976 (Box 234)
      - Script - Frank Waldman. (Box 234)
      - First revised draft: (Waldman)., July 1, 1976 (Box 234)
      - Second revision, July 19, 1976. (Box 234)
      - Second revision, July 28, 1976. (Box 234)
      - Second revision., August 23, 1976. (Box 234)
      - Third revision, September 13, 1976. (Box 234)
      - First draft, revised with third and fourth revisions. and, September 17, 1976 September 27, 1976. (Box 235)
      - First draft, revised, (2)., November 24, 1976 (Box 235)
      - First draft, revised, (2)., December 1, 1976 (Box 235)
      - First draft, revised, (6)., December 1, 1976 (Box 236)
      - Third revision. (Box 237)
      - Revised pages - General (folder). (Box 237)
      - Miscellaneous pages - approximately 200. From Sherman. (Box 237)
      - File Copies (Sanford Sherman). (5) First revised draft:, December 15, 1975. (Box 237)
      - First draft:, July 28, 1975. (Box 237)
      - Various revised pages (SK) (accordion file). (Box 238)
      - Pp. 30-51. (Box 238)
      - Revised pages. Varied. Frank Waldman. (Box 238)
      - File copy. Second revision, and fourth revision, March 11, 1976 September 26, 1976. (Box 238)
  - Ship of Fools, 1965.
    - Final draft by Abby Mann. (Box 73)
    - Magnetic sound track, Bosley Crother. (Box 73)
    - Folder of awards. (Box 73)
    - Revised shooting schedule, August 13, 1964.; (folder) (Box 251)
    - Horwitz, A1 - EXPENSES., (folder) (Box 251)
    - Budget--ESTIMATED DETAIL., (folder) (Box 251)
    - Budget--COST REPORTS., (folder) (Box 251)
    - dialogue continuity (Box 368, Folder 1)
    - cutting continuity (Folder 2)
    - Script, final. (Box 251)
    - Script., May 18, 1964. (Box 251)
    - Comments, etc., (folder) (Box 251)
    - Stills, 1 piece. (Box 299, Folder 4)
    - 35 mm black and white print, credits only. (Box 325)
    - Six transcription records. (Box 325)
    - Production files (Actors' Contracts - Biographies). (Box 73)
    - Production files (Call sheets - Music breakdown). (Box 74)
    - Production files (Music titles - Proofs of Porter novel). (Box 75)
    - Production files (Publicity - Zagon). (Box 76)
    - 500 production stills, 8 × 10. (Box 77, Box 78)
    - Ship of Fools, spots one through five by Stan Freberg., 2 tapes. (Box 111)
    - Replica of a boat given by Spencer Tracy to Stanley Kramer for Ship of Fools. (Box 332)
    - Press clippings. (Box 367)
    - Agreement (Box 251)
    - Stanley Warner Theatres Plaque for Ship of Fools, 1965. (Box 331)
    - M. Beck Publicity and Correspondence. Releases (Box 130)
    - M. Beck Publicity and Correspondence. Reviews (Box 130)
    - M. Beck Publicity and Correspondence. Schedules (Box 130)
    - M. Beck Publicity and Correspondence. Tear Sheets (Box 130)
    - M. Beck Publicity and Correspondence. New York University (Box 130)
    - Tape Recordings
      - Fund for the Republic press conference, one hour. (Box 110)
      - Judgement at Nuremberg. (Box 110)
      - Film Editors Seminar: interview of Stanley Kramer. (Box 110)
      - Dateline, July 21, 1957. (Box 110)
      - Mike Wallace interview. (Box 110)
      - Laugh tracks on running for UCLA students, two parts, March 11, 1963.; 2 tapes. (Box 110)
      - Hebrew. Israel. (Box 110)
      - The Changing Face of Hollywood, two parts. 2 tapes. (Box 110)
      - On the Beach. Melbourne, Australia, radio station. (Box 111)
      - RPM. Lecture by Stanley Kramer at the University of the Pacific, December 1969. (Box 111)
      - United World Federation banquet, May 1, 1960. (Box 111)
      - Whittinghill Show, November 11, 1963. (Box 111)
      - ABC Academy show re Irving Thalberg Award to Stanley Kramer, April 9, 1962.; One tape and one record. (Box 111)
      - Vivian Leigh Appreciation at USC, March 17, 1968. (Box 111)
      - Dialogue between Professor Feinstein, UC Berkeley, and Stanley Kramer on Guess Who's Coming to Dinner, 1968. (Box 111)
      - NYU Dinner, Plaza Hotel, New York City, December 4, 1968. (Box 111)
      - Joel Spivak and Stanley Kramer, December 6, 1967. (Box 111)
      - Dick Strout, Sidney Poitier and Katherine Hepburn, August 10, 1967. (Box 111)
      - Press conference: English Teachers' Seminar, March 2, 1968. (Box 111)
      - The Secret of Santa Vittoria. (Box 111)
      - Miscellaneous interviews. (Box 112)
        - Interview for Frank Tallman special on KOCE-TV. Tape cassette and typed transcription. (Box 112)
  - The Sniper, 1952.
    - Final shooting script. (Box 4)
    - Script, (2)., September 4, 1951 (Box 252)
    - Dialogue continuity. (Box 252)
    - Folder of newsclippings. (Box 4)
    - Production breakdown. (Box 4)
    - 16 × 20 framed still photograph (Arthur Franz).
    - 16 Storyboards. (Box 374, Folder 9)
    - 35 Storyboards fromsection labeled Eddie Come Home Final. (Box 374, Folder 8)
    - 35 Storyboards from section labeled Eddie Over Sleeps. (Box 374, Folder 7)
    - 38 Storyboards from section labeled Emergency Hospital (Box 374, Folder 6)
    - 35 Storyboards from section labeled Walk In Park, Drug Store. (Box 374, Folder 5)
  - So Ends Our Night
  - So This is New York
    - Scrapbook of So Ends Our Night and So This is New York, 1940-1946. (Box 328)
    - Scrapbook of So Ends Our Night and So This is New York (Box 328)
    - 16 × 20 framed still photograph (Henry Morgan).
  - The Wild One, 1954.
    - Final shooting script, heavily annotated. (Box 6)
    - 16 × 20 framed still photograph (Marlon Brando).
    - Script. Final draft: Screenplay by John Paxton., January 20, no year. (Box 298)
    - The Wild One (Box 298)
  - Russian Film (produced and directed in Moscow by Stanley Kramer).
    - 15 reels of film, interviews. (Box 108)
    - Correspondence. (Box 109)
    - Brochures and photographs. (Box 109)
    - Press clippings. (Box 367)
  - M. Beck Publicity and Correspondence Files
- Correspondence and Memorabilia
  - Academy Awards and nominations correspondence, 1949-1968. (Box 113)
  - American Film Institute (George Stevens, Jr.) correspondence. (Box 113)
  - American Jewish Committee correspondence. (Box 113)
  - Big Town correspondence. (Box 113)
  - Fund for the Republic, Incorporated, correspondence. (Box 113)
  - Hollywood Museum Associates correspondence. (Box 113)
  - Knickerbocker (San Francisco Chronicle) correspondence, 1963. (Box 113)
  - Leigh, Vivien Appreciation at USC correspondence, March 17, 1968. (Box 113)
  - Thank you letters - Stanley Kramer. (Box 113)
  - USIA, Washington, D.C. (George Stevens, Jr.) correspondence. (Box 113)
  - Western Behavioral Sciences Institute. (Box 113)
  - Wilshire Boulevard Temple, Los Angeles. (Box 113)
  - 50th Birthday book, September 29, 1963. (Box 114)
  - Stanley Kramer personal awards and miscellaneous correspondence, 92 pp. (Box 114)
  - UCLA Extension,, correspondence, 101 pages., 1963 (Box 114)
  - UCLA Extension,, correspondence, 34 pages., 1963 (Box 114)
  - UCLA Extension,, correspondence, 71 pages, 1963 (Box 114)
  - UC Berkeley correspondence, 11 pp. (Box 114)
  - UCLA Material donations correspondence. (Box 114)
  - USC correspondence. (Box 114)
  - American Legion, 214 letters. (Box 115)
  - American Legion, 16 letters. (Box 115)
  - American Legion newspaper and trade publication clippings, 72 files. (Box 115)
  - Ahab (Sidney Poitier), 10 letters. (Box 115)
  - Governor Ellis Arnoll, 4 letters. (Box 115)
  - Note of Appreciation brochure by Stanley Kramer to directors, writers and cast. (Box 115)
  - Esquire magazine article, The Summer Job I Had As a Boy, June 1968. (Box 115)
  - Saturday Review article on Stanley Kramer, March 14, 1953. (Box 115)
  - Jack Valenti to Kramer re trip to Moscow, two letters. (Box 115)
  - Katherine Hepburn, Katherine Houghton and Spencer Tracy to Karen Kramer on birth of baby., One letter. (Box 115)
  - Karlovy-Vary Festival certificate for Guess Who's Coming to Dinner, 1968. (Box 115)
  - First draft of Final Verdict by Elizabeth Wilson. Screenplay, March 9, 1964. (Box 115)
  - First draft of Flotsam by David Loew and Albert Lewin, heavily annotated. Screenplay. (Box 115)
- Awards and Memorabilia
  - The Albert Gallatin Award, at New York University., December 4, 1968 (Box 116)
    - Seven dinner program brochures, December 4, 1968. (Box 116)
    - Sixteen photographs of the dinner program. In scrapbook. (Box 116)
    - Bronze medallion given to Kramer at the dinner program. (Box 116)
  - American Jewish Committee, Anti-Defamation League, B'nai Brith Plaque, 1961. (Box 331)
  - American Jewish Committee Human Relations--W.J. German Award, 1967. (Box 118)
  - American Jewish Congress arts award, January 18, 1968. (Box 116)
  - Berlin Film Festival bronze medallion, 1952. (Box 118)
  - Black Filmmakers Hall of Fame Honorary Award, 1976. (Box 280)
  - B'nai Brith Man of the Year Award, encased medallion, 1970-1971. (Box 341)
  - B'nai Brith Women's Plaque for Humanitarian, 1962. (Box 331)
  - Brandeis University Library--Learned Research Journal. (Box 278)
  - California Fashion Creators Trophy, 1953. (Box 359)
  - California Teachers' Association Trophy, 1968. (Box 328)
  - California Youth Gives a Damn Coalition, 1972-1976. (Box 278)
  - Chicago International Film Festival citation of merit. (Box 117)
  - Cine-Revue gold medallion. (Box 117)
  - City of Hope statue for Outstanding Service, 1951. (Box 330)
  - City of Hope Torch Bearer Award, 1955. (Box 330)
  - Cork International Film Festival Silver Trophy, 1966. (Box 328)
  - UCLA plexi-glass award, charter member, Murphy Associates. (Box 118)
  - Exhibitor Laurel Award for top ten producers and directors, 1966. (Box 116)
  - Irving Thalberg Memorial Award, 1961. (Box 332)
  - Jewish Federation Council of Los Angeles, plaque, 1968. (Box 357)
  - Jewish Home for the Aged The Guardians plaque, 1962. (Box 121)
  - Look Award, (medallion)., 1950 (Box 278)
  - Look magazine plaque for film achievement, 1950. (Box 116)
  - Los Angeles Film Teachers' Association Parchment, 1969. (Box 328)
    Item moved to Box 357
  - Los Angeles International Film Exposition - Participation,, for High Noon and The Member of the Wedding., March 21-April 4, 1976 (Box 357)
  - Maschera d'Argento plaque, Rome, 1967-1968. (Box 117)
  - La Mejor Pelicula Extranjera (MCMLIII) green and bronze award. (Box 117)
  - La Mostra Internazionale d'Arte Cinema Diveneza gold medallion, 1960. (Box 117)
  - NAACP Image Award. Special Award., 1972 (Box 335)
  - New York University Achievement Award plaque, 17 May 1966. (Box 116)
  - New York University Man of the Year Testimonial Plaque, 1967. (Box 328)
  - New York University Perstare et Praestare plaque (MDCCCXXXI). (Box 117)
  - Pewter mug - New York University Alumni Fun, 1966. (Box 332)
  - Norske Konosjefers Tildelt de Skalarve Vinden Forbund Solvklumpen silver plaque, 1965. (Box 118)
  - One book, Year of 1949 - Outstanding Man. (Box 328)
  - Prix Femina du Cinema Hommage gold medallion, 1960. (Box 117)
  - Producers' Guild plexi-glass award for Producer of the Year, 1967. (Box 118)
  - Screen Directors' Guild bronze award. (Box 117)
  - Silver-Sindacto Giorvalisti Cinema Italiani silver medallion, 1962. (Box 117)
  - Statues, male (2) Bookends. (Box 279)
  - Terneo preolimpico, (medallion)., 1949 (Box 278)
  - Trophy, pendant and certificate, Phi Eta Sigma of UCLA,, Honorary Life Member, Stanley Kramer., 1970 (Box 332)
  - United Jewish Welfare Plaque for Man of the Year, 1960. (Box 330)
  - Unity Award plaque for human relations, 1966. (Box 121)
  - University of Southern California Citation of Appreciation. (Box 334)